All right, welcome guys. So, I just made
this new mirror board basically how I
make 2K to 100K dollars per post on X.
So, basically I have four case studies
for you guys. Um four different
accounts, four different posts. Of
course, I have like thousands of
different case studies that I could post
about. I have thousands of these, but I
just picked out four uh notable ones for
you guys. Michael, uh he's case study
number one and how I made 100K uh from
one post for him. This is case study
number two, my account. I made 30K from
this one post. Uh this is case study
number three, Aryan doing 10K to 1.5
million per post. Um and then case study
number four is Parker, he's my partner
basically how I ran up his X uh and how
we did 570,000 dollars in three months.
All right? So,
uh four case studies for you guys. What
do I do? So, I make posts on X, on
Twitter, very high quality ones, and we
sell lots of digital products, ebooks,
courses, coachings, uh services, done
for you stuff like that. Anywhere
between like 50 dollars to
uh like 30,000 dollars sell. All right?
So, let me show you guys just proof of
this uh Stripe sales dashboard. So, in
the past seven days you can see that we
did 151,000
dollars in sales, right? All right, so
each day you can see how much we made
here, and then so
uh past four weeks, how much we did past
four weeks? 176,000 dollars.
Um and in the past uh six months, um I
actually don't know. 2.7 million
dollars. And then past 12 months, so I I
think I started this account around like
10 months ago. So, I made 3.87 million
dollars within the past 12 months. So,
you can see here like some days we have
two days we where we crossed 100,000
dollar days, but you know, that's
basically just proof to show you guys um
how much we're making. So, basically you
saw the sales dashboard, and so now who
is this video for? Who is this YouTube
video for? What am I going to show you
guys? So, basically it's if you are
already selling high ticket stuff
online, or you know, if you're
interested in learning how this all
works. So, my promise to you is that I'm
going to show you exactly how I make
these posts, how the funnel works, so
exactly what happens after, so exactly
what the audience, the customer goes
through step by step by step, and how
you can recreate it, too, and then make
these sales. So, I'm going to show you
everything that you need to know,
basically revealing everything. I'm not
going to be hiding everything by the end
of this. Basically, by the end of this
I'm going to feel like I'm completely
naked because I'm showing you
everything, right? This video is just
going to be focused on the high ticket
sales, right? I do both low ticket and
high ticket. I sell both cheap and
expensive stuff, but this video is just
going to be focused on high ticket,
meaning expensive stuff. So, anything
more than 1,000 dollars per sale, right?
So, if you want to learn how this works
for just digital products in general,
then I have a 90-minute uh YouTube video
which you can watch here if you want
after this video or now you can do that.
But, anyways, let's dive into this
mirror board going by case by case. All
right? So, this is case study number
one. I recently basically TLDR I made
one single post, first try, that made
100,000 dollars for my friend named
Michael. So, Michael and I were friends.
So, he's in LA, right? Uh so, he just
like sends me a message. He's like,
"Hey, can you help me with my X?" And
I'm like, "Got you. Uh just send me your
address. I'll be I'll come over, you
know." And then so, you know, this is
him. This is him. He sells AI
uh systems to big companies. So,
basically in easy words, what he does is
that he helps companies to become more
efficient, saving lots of time
um so that they can make more, right?
So, uh for example, there are just CEOs
out there that are working 58 hours per
week, but after he automates their
business and makes them more efficient
with AI, he ends up uh spending 25 hours
per week. Same work, just like more
efficiency, so it takes less time to
complete the same thing, right? And then
his AI system, automation system,
basically helped increase the valuation
of the company from 493,000 dollars to
1.6 million dollars.
Spending 70 hours
uh and then he also helped increase the
profit margins from 22% to 35%. All
right? So,
um
this is the post that he made for
himself. Uh it didn't get many uh likes
or engagement, right? 600 views, seven
likes, two comments. Uh but basically I
took this post and I reworded it. Um
basically the same exact content, but I
fixed the header, fixed the words, uh
put in a little bit more information,
and I spent 10 minutes making this and I
got 13,000 views and 156 comments,
right? And then uh I was specifically
targeting people who are business
owners. So, like each person can
comfortably, easily spend like 10,000 or
50,000 dollars because, you know, these
people are operating million dollar
companies. So, each one of these people
operating
huge companies. Um so, that was a very
intentional. Because of the copywriting,
because of the writing of this post, it
attracted these kinds of very high level
people, right? So, let me give you a
quick copywriting course, okay? So, it
all starts with the header. It all
starts with the header. So, in the very
beginning, I made it bold, basically
exactly what we did to raise the company
valuation from All right, so the first
line is the most most most important.
It's just the hook, the header. Before
the heck the the hook was this. But then
I change it, I rewrite the post so that
it's raised the company from 493,000 to
1.6 million in valuation. That's a much
bolder and interesting hook that is
going to attract the attention of many
people. I try to put I try to put as
many numbers in the post as possible
because it keeps things specific,
detailed, and interesting. Because
otherwise it's going to sound broad and
uninteresting. So, you want to include
as many numbers as you can. All right?
So, the rest of the tweet is the body.
It's just the details. So, the founder
was overworking, you know, this he was
doing this, things were terrible. This
is information, and then this is exactly
what he did uh exactly what he did for
them. You know, so bullet points that
makes it very uh interesting, nice
format to read uh compared to earlier.
Um and then the results, you know,
including a lot of numbers again. I
reduced the workload of the CEO from 58
hours to 25 hours with
uh the same exact work, right? So, just
making things more efficient with the
AI. And then
our profit margin increased from 22% to
35% and blah blah blah, right? Exact
same operations, exact same work, it's
just things are more efficient because
of the AI that Michael implemented into
the business, right? Okay. So,
um at the very end is the CTA, the call
to action. Basically, you want people to
read it, you know, in the very beginning
you want to stop people from scrolling,
actually read it, become interested in
reading more, which is the body for more
details. The body will make the viewer
more interested and want to learn more,
and at the very end is the offer,
basically what you are pitching to the
viewer, right? So, here basically, you
can see that I'm offering five things.
And obviously like before he was only
offering just one like vague line that
seems very small. But obviously having
five things with a lot of numbers, this
sounds a lot lot more valuable than what
he was providing earlier, right? And
also, you know, and also like this is a
much uh better format to read than this,
more information, more numbers, more
specific, more details. It's basically
like a storytelling within a post.
Basically, the first line is, you know,
to establish authority. Why should
people listen to you? To get people's
attention, and then you want to, you
know, write it like a story. In the
beginning it was like this, but then we
we did this, and then this was the
result. So, it's very very interesting.
And then the offer at the very end, you
know, if people want all five of these,
then just comment blueprint, and you'll
get all of this. And then I had people,
I forced people to follow and retweet in
order to get these five things. So,
whenever people comment, it will
basically force the Twitter algorithm to
reach out to more people to show it to,
basically. So, you know, we did this
many engagement, and then people will
post, right? High quality people,
verified people. Many of these are in
the US who are business owners can
easily spend like 10 to 50K each, right?
High quality people, each of these
people with lots of money, right? And
you can see that we did that for 156
people. And then so, you know, when you
look at 13,000 views, it might not seem
like a lot. It's very little. But
actually, you know, this post made
100,000
dollars. It made 100,000 dollars, and I
can prove to you that uh these kinds of
posts are making a lot lot lot more than
posts are getting millions of views.
Like later I'll show you accounts like
my friends who have millions of
followers, millions of views every
single day, but are barely making
anything. Views over account does not
mean anything. It's irrelevant to how
much money you're making, all right? So,
you could be even making just 2,000 or
3,000 views per post, and you could be
making so much money with it. It's just
a targeting problem. Who you're
targeting? Are you targeting high
quality people? And are you converting
those people, making them interested,
converting them into sales, right? It's
a skill problem. So, for me, I focus on
getting little views, and then, you
know, converting very highly. All right?
And uh
ultimately the people that you attract,
high level people with a lot of money to
spend, there's not going to be too many
of them, right? That's why we only got
13,000 views and not like millions
because, you know, the reality is that
there aren't millions of people who are
high level like that. If I targeted to
more people and like focus on getting
like a million views, then I'll be
making less money, right? That's just
like a paradox, like the irony of
posting, right? And then I also retweet
from some of my big accounts. So, I own
many accounts, many of them are big,
retweet them to give it a boost. And so,
it got a bit more engagement than
normally. There's also this thing called
the 10-minute rule. Basically, uh the
first 10 minutes after you make a post
is
basically the indicator to how much
engagement your post will make. So, you
know, if you get a lots of engagement,
comments, and likes, and retweets within
the first 10 minutes, then your post is
going to do absolutely great within the
next 48 to 72 hours, right? So, within
the first 10 minutes, you want to
basically maximize the engagement,
basically post when your audience is
awake. I mean, I can teach you how to do
that later, basically see you when your
audience is most active. Because the
reality is that the reality is that the
timing of your post matters a lot. You
want to know exactly when your followers
are active and post it then. You know,
that way you're going to get lots of
engagement. And of course, again, the
quality of the audience that you
attract, the quality of the people that
comment on your post is a reflection of
the copy, of the words uh are from this
post. All right, so that's very, very
important. Um if you post like just dumb
stuff, you're going to attract dumb
people. If you attract like high-quality
stuff, catered to entrepreneurs,
high-level entrepreneurs, then you're
going to attract the same exact people,
right? So, you know, basically
uh you see that you a lot of people will
comment. So, whenever someone comments
on the video, or no, whenever someone
comments on the X post, uh they will
automatically receive uh these things
that he promised within DM. So, as soon
as someone comments, it'll automatically
be sent to the DM. All right, so, you
have to notice two things is that
um you can see that he's replying to
every single comment, which is a very
important for two reasons. One, it
reminds these people who commented to
check their DMs because that is going to
increase the conversion, right? The more
people who check the DMs, the more
people you're going to convert. And
then, second thing is basically to
encourage others who are seeing the post
for the first time to comment, right?
They're getting FOMO. Um they're getting
basically this jealousy, this fear of
missing out uh for not commenting. You
know, they're going to want it, too. So,
basically encourages more people to
comment. Because, you know, the reality
is that there are so many posts on X
that are engagement farming that are not
actually delivering on the promise. So,
this is really proof to uh
make many people comfortable to post,
right?
to post the comment. And you can see
here again that a lot of these people
who comment are high-quality people,
they're all verified uh check-marked. Uh
you know, they have a lot of money each.
So, you want to target very high-quality
people who have lots of money to spend
each of them. All right? So, uh this is
what each person who comments will
receive in their DM. So, this message
saying, you know, details, and then fill
out this form to move forward to the
next steps. Generally, around like 50%
of these people will end up clicking on
that and uh you know, working through
the form. So, you can see here that this
is what the form looks like, you know,
basically to qualify the leads, you have
this form. And you know, this post
basically made $100,000.
He's selling these AI systems for
anywhere between 10 to $100,000
per sale. So, it really depends on the
company size and what their needs are,
right? Uh so, you know, it doesn't take
a lot of sales to get to $100,000
uh in sales. All right? So,
this is what the form looks like. And
you know, he texts me like I think
probably like two days later saying,
"Wow, this post popped off, $100,000 in
deal flow." And then, yeah, I won't
exactly reveal how much he's making like
every month, but this post, you know,
$97,000
in cash collected. Basically, he sent me
this screenshot, right? And then,
generally, people will take around a
week or within a week, they will get
from seeing the post to making the
payment. Of course, there's a slight
delay. It's like, you know, seeing the
tweet, taking action based off that, uh
filling out the form, and doing the
call, making the payment, usually
there's like a 7-day delay or so. All
right? You know, that's just universal
for all the posts that I make. Usually,
there's like a delay, like a few days
until they actually make the payment,
right? So, it took me like 10 minutes to
make the tweet, if not like less, and we
made $100,000 from this one post, right?
So, you know, if you do the math, that's
around $10,000 per minute spent
basically that I did writing this post,
which is not too bad. So, that's the
power of copywriting. If you understand
how to put these words together to
attract the attention of people,
high-quality people, and to read through
all this kind of like a storytelling
method, and then to have this offer
where people comment and then go through
this funnel, basically, you'll be making
a lot of money. So, this is case study
number two, basically how I made $30,000
from this one post right here, this
post. All right? So, I'm selling this
something for $5,000, and we made six
sales, so $30,000. Again, it's the same
thing, you know, like a bold header with
numbers, and then like a 10-step process
of the details, the technical side of
things, and at the very end, there's an
offer, right? If you want the full
65-page guide, the ebook, then just
comment PDF to get it. All right? So,
it's the same exact process, you know,
300,000 views. Of course, not every post
is going to be getting 300,000 views,
but I'm making these kinds of posts
every single day, usually like at least
like two or three of these every single
day, and you know, we're generating
hundreds or thousands of leads every
single day, and we're making thousands.
As you can see again, uh I get lots of
comments on my post. Actually, funny
thing, Richard Yu, he's my friend, he
makes over 500k uh per month.
So, that's very interesting that I had
he commented on my post. I didn't
realize that until now. But anyways, you
know, I didn't have the time to reply to
everyone just cuz there were too many
people that I had to reply to, so I
didn't do that. But you know, I
encourage you to reply to every single
comment if you can, like like Michael
did here. But in my case, I was getting
too much, so I couldn't I physically
couldn't do that. Um but you know, these
are all high-quality leads. These are
verified people with money, they're in
the US. And then, it automatically sends
this, you know, free video and the ebook
that I promised to every single one of
these people. Every single day, I'm
sending hundreds of thousands of these
messages to basically those who comment
or like my videos every single day,
right? I'm sending this out. So, So, I'm
sending like thousands of DMs every
single day with my free material. And uh
you can see here that's around 35% of my
audience is US, which is something that
you should be striving for.
Um you can see the age demographic, uh
other details, when my audience is most
active. So, if you go to settings, you
can see that. And then, basically, they
get two videos. By the way, these two
YouTube videos have combined in more
than $100,000 in sales. So, you know,
that's very good as well. Um so, in the
bio of these videos, basically, there is
like a Typeform. There's a form for
people to apply to my mentorship
program, which I'm selling for $5,000,
right? So, I've gotten
thousands of people to submit. On
Typeform, I've gotten 885 submissions
within the past few weeks. And in Tally,
I've gotten 2,700 people to apply for my
5K coaching, right? And so, inside my
program, I basically teach how to do all
this to, you know, basically make posts
um targeting high-quality people. Uh
it's organic, how to go viral, basically
how to convert those views into sales,
right? How to do the conversion.
Basically teaching you how to
convert these viewers, uh these views
into sales, right? Uh and teaching the
systems, automations, how to automate
everything, how to scale
uh to six figures per month.
All right, so, you know, I do cap this
program to max like 10 to 20 students
per month, which is less than 10%
acceptance rate, but you know, this is
alone is making me six figures per
month. Um which I could do a lot more if
I wanted to, but just I have limited
time, limited people that I can help.
So, that's why I keep it a very little,
but you can see the sales that I'm
making here. And this is basically how
much I've made across all my accounts
all combined. So, doing a few million
per year, right? So, this is case study
number two done. All right, case study
number three is going to be a bit
shorter. Uh it's my friend who's also in
LA.
Basically, all three of us were good
friends here in LA.
Uh we're all like in our early 20s, but
he has an X account, and he also has a
LinkedIn account, right? Basically doing
very similar things where he's making
posts, exact same format again, like a
like header and then a body, you know,
bullet points for nice formatting, and
we have a call to action at the very
end, right? If you want this, then
comment this, and the DM you like the
whatever system. 1,500 comments,
basically exact same framework that I'm
using uh for myself and for Michael. Um
and then people basically book a call,
and then his clients usually pay
anywhere between $10,000 to $1.5
million, right? So, he has his clients
are basically paying him a lot, and he
usually has around five to 10 of these
sales every month, right? But I can't
reveal too much details because, you
know, he's pretty strict. He has a few
NDAs. But anyways, you know, he's doing
pretty, pretty well. He's doing pretty
well. You can read his story. He was
literally like homeless like two years
ago, or maybe a year ago, I don't know,
in Dubai. But now he is comfortably
spending like, you know,
uh low five figures just on housing plus
his Porsche 911. So, you know, he's
doing very well. All right, so, case
study number four, this is my friend
named Parker who's actually originally
my student, but we started working
together, partnering, working together.
So, this is the kind of post we make,
again, a nice header hook. We have the
body, and then we have the call to
action at the very end, comment AI, and
you get a free course. So, you know,
people comment, and they would
automatically receive uh a link to join
the Discord, right, in their DMs. So,
they In the Discord, there are like, you
know, free documents, basically where
people learn. And at the very end, you
know if they're interested they can
apply for Parker's coaching. So
basically they fill out a form. 1,800
people filled out the form. And by the
way we only had this program available.
This account was only running for 3
months in the summer. We had 1,800
people apply for this coaching and then
577 calls out of the 1,824. So around
like a third of those people who filled
out the application actually booked the
call and then we had around like 25%
close rate. I don't know the
percentage but you know 132 people
bought for you know it was 5K each but
we gave some people discounts like the
average turned out to be like 4.3
thousand. And so we made $570,000
within a 3-month period, right? All
right. So more of the details of what we
sold, what we gave to the clients, what
they got. So they got a community, they
got a 3-month access to the Discord
community to learn, collaborate with
other students, learn from each other,
do whatever. And then of course there
courses in there. So you know basically
video content, document content so that
they can learn
how to basically make money with AI
models which of course Parker is
experienced with. And then you know he
offers a one-on-one coaching, right?
From Parker. And of course some students
actually started making money for
themselves so they also became
co-coaches. And there was also 7-day
guarantee. So if anyone was not
satisfied with the purchase they could
get their money back. All right. So
$570,000
cumulatively within 3 months and this
post this post alone made six sales,
$27,000, right? With only 159 comments
which is And so we just keep repeating
these kinds of posts every single day,
all right? And I know that we made we
make bold claims but these are actually
true. Like these numbers are true. I
don't encourage any of you guys to lie
or make up any numbers. We can only say
stuff that is true that we actually did,
right? So you know my goal has obviously
made millions with AI. I have made
millions with you know what I do. Parker
has made millions with AI models.
Uh
you know Aryan here has made millions
with just AI in general with chatbots
and stuff like that.
Parker has made millions with AI models.
So you know we're actually posting real
stuff, real case studies, real numbers.
So none of this is false. This is all
real. So you know if you don't have any
experience highly discourage you to make
any of these stuff up because you know
you're not going to be able to get any
sales in the first place, right? Okay.
So we did $570,000 in 3-month period
which is around
almost 200K per month. Uh split 50/50
with Parker so that each of us got
$285,000
with just one account over 3 months. So
that's case study number four.
>> [clears throat]
>> You know
on the on the other side I want to show
you accounts that are basically getting
millions of views, millions of followers
that are barely making any money. So
these are two accounts for example 6.5
million followers this account got, 1.3
million followers. And these are the
posts that they're making. You know
they're getting more than millions of
views per post, getting huge engagement
but the reality is that the quality of
that audience is just so low that
they're not making anything, right? This
guy for example he like DM'd me and said
like you know can you help me to get up
to 15K per month or 50K per month.
So you know they're making a lot less
than that. They're barely they're
they're barely making anything. The
quality of the audience is just so low
and plus like they don't know how to
monetize their audience at all. They
don't know how to create a product, they
don't know how to sell. Um so they're
barely making anything despite having
millions of followers and getting
millions of views every day. All right.
This is another account. This guy he's
like pitching me let's work together.
And I'm like I'm like sure. Okay. I'll
help you out. But then you know he just
ends up not wanting to work with me.
He's saying that you know I still
haven't monetized this account. I've
offered to help him lots but you know
basically he has the fear of me
basically building out the funnel,
creating the products for some reason.
So basically still to still to this day
he's not making anything. But you know
this is just to show you that follower
count and view count is not important,
is not relevant at all to like how much
money you're making cuz these accounts
are doing millions of views, millions of
followers and they're not making
anything versus these posts that are
barely getting like 10 or 50,000 views
are just making you know thousands of
dollars per post, right? So really views
and followers are completely irrelevant.
It's really all about the quality that
you're posting, quality of the post,
quality of the content, quality of the
audience and how well you're able to
convert that audience into sales, right?
So that's what's most important. That's
going to break or make how much you're
you're making. So you know each of these
accounts are doing more than $100,000
per month just posting simple tweets
that take a few seconds or a few minutes
to make per post, right? This is why I
basically focus on getting less views
but targeting a higher quality audience
because I know that you know I could be
making millions of views but I'm going
to attract a very low quality audience
which I don't want that. I want to
target you know people in the US,
Canada, people who are wealthy, smart
entrepreneurs who can easily spend
thousands of dollars you know
comfortably without hesitating at all.
So that's why each of these accounts are
making more than $100,000
per month. So if you got this far I have
two things that I'm offering for you. So
one is basically if you're already doing
more than $50,000 per month just selling
stuff online with high tickets then you
know you can apply to work with me and
I'll generate for you an extra minimum
$100,000 per month from this new X post
that I make for you, all right? And then
number two is you know if you just want
to join my mentorship program I can
teach you basically how to make these
kinds of posts and how to generate leads
and clients and then to basically split
profits with partners to find and sell
these high ticket items, all right? And
I can basically be coaching you every
single day. Some of my students also
have become successful themselves so
they are co-coaches. We will help you
every single day so that you're on the
right progress right path to be making
similar numbers to these, all right? And
then if you want to learn more of the
details you know this was a very short
video but if you want to learn more of
the details then I have this 90-minute
crash course right here that you can
watch. It'll give you all the
information you need. So I highly
recommend checking that out. But anyways
I hope this video has been helpful and
probably going to get some dinner in
pretty soon. So I'll see you guys later.
Peace.